ILGWU David Dubinsky Correspondence 5780/002
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Joint Board. and D.C. N.Y. Dress Jt. Bd., 1933 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  I.c.w. Philip Kapp; address by D.D. at Dressmakers' Victory Rally, 10-4-33; leaflets on strike.
- Joint Board. and D.C. N.Y. Ladies Apparel Accessories Council, 1936-1939 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  Reports; official list of Union accessory shops in the Ladies Apparel Industry; Union shops in Dress Industry, 1937.
- Joint Board. and D.C. Philadelphia Cloak Jt. Bd., 1940-1950 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  Corres. w. Harry Dordick.
- Joint Board. and D.C. Phila. Cloak Jt. Bd., 1928-1939 (Box 69, Folder 5a-5b)
  I.c.w. Louis Bulkin, George Rubin; Special Comm. Report on Merger and Separation of Locals 2 & 17.
- Joint Board. and D.C. Phila. Dress Jt. Bd., 1939-1950 (Box 69, Folder 6a-6b)
  Incl. arbitration hearing, Adella Dress Co. Case, 1950; correspondence. w. Samuel Otto, re_ Biberman Bros., Inc.
- Joint Board. and D.C. Phila. Dress Jt. Bd., 1942-1946 (Box 69, Folder 7)
- Joint Board. and D.C. Phila. Dress Jt. Bd., 1939-1941 (Box 70, Folder 1)
- Joint Board. and D.C. Phila. Dress Jt. Bd., 1936-1938 (Box 70, Folder 2a-2b)
- Joint Board. and D.C. Phila. Dress Jt. Bd., 1934-1935 (Box 70, Folder 3a-3b)
  I.c.w. Elias Reisberg.
- Joint Board. and D.C. Phila. Dress Jt. Bd., 1933 (Box 70, Folder 4)
- Joint Board. and D.C. Phila. Jt. Council, 1936-1950 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  I.c.w. Louis Bulkin.
- Joint Board. and D.C. San Francisco Joint Board., 1937-1939 (Box 70, Folder 6a-6b)
  I.c.w. Jennie Matyas; proceedings of Exec. Bd., Local 8 Committee investigating charges against Ted Goldstein, Dec. 1937.
- Joint Board. and D.C. San Francisco Jt. Bd., 1936 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  Incl. report to the GEB at the Jt. meeting held w. Exec. Bds. of the S.F. locals, May 1936; correspondence. on Diner case.
- Joint Board. and D.C. San Francisco Jt. Bd., 1934-1935 (Box 71, Folder 1a-1c)
  Nov. 1934-Dec. 1935.
- Joint Board. and D.C. San Francisco Jt. Bd., 1933-1934 (Box 71, Folder 2a-2c)
  Mar. 1933-34. I.c.w. Samuel S. White.
- Joint Board. and D.C. Scranton Jt. Bd., 1940-1949 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  I.c.w. I. Zimmerman, Elias Reisberg.
- Joint Board. and D.C. Scranton District Council, 1933-1939 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  Incl. correspondence. re Royal Miss Dress Co.
- Joint Board. and D.C. Seattle Joint Board., 1947-1950 (Box 71, Folder 5)
  I.c.w. Eloise Pratt, Mabel Sundberg.
- Joint Board. and D.C. Seattle Jt. Bd., 1940-1946 (Box 71, Folder 6a-6b)
- Joint Board. and D.C. Seattle Jt. Bd., 1933-1939 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  I.c.w. Harold Hibbard, Eugene Glasser.
- Joint Board. and D.C. So. Jersey Jt. Bd., 1939 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  I.c.w. Barnett Karp.
- Joint Board. and D.C. So. Jersey Jt. Bd., 1937-1938 (Box 72, Folder 3a-3b)
- Joint Board. and D.C. So. Jersey Jt. Bd., 1933-1936 (Box 72, Folder 4a-4c)
- Joint Board. and D.C. St. Louis Cloak & Dress Jt. Bd., 1940-1948 (Box 72, Folder 5a-5b)
  I.c.w. Meyer Perlstein.
- Joint Board. and D.C. St. Louis Jt. Bd., 1936-1939 (Box 72, Folder 6a-6b)
  I.c.w. Ben Gilbert.
- Joint Board. and D.C. St. Louis Jt. Bd., 1934-1935 (Box 73, Folder 1a-1c)
  Incl. petition by Local 104 members to GEB not to remove Edith Phillips as organizer, 1934.
- Joint Board. and D.C. St. Louis Jt. Bd., 1937-1939 (Box 73, Folder 2a-2b)
  Forest City Mfr. Co., I.c.w. Meyer Perlstein & firms re collective agreement.
- Joint Board. and D.C. St. Louis Jt. Bd., 1935 (Box 73, Folder 3a)
  Forest City Mfr. Co. I.c.w. Meyer Perlstein, Elias Lieberman & Forest City Co. re strike & settlement 1935; findings of comm. appointed by St. Louis Chamber of Commerce.
- Joint Board. and D.C. St. Louis Jt. Bd., 1933 (Box 73, Folder 3b)
  I.c.w. I. Halpern, Bernard Shane & Edith Phillips.
- Joint Board. and D.C. Toronto Jt. Bd., 1947-1950 (Box 73, Folder 4a-4b)
  I.c.w. S. Kraisman, re displaced persons.
- Joint Board. and D.C. Toronto Jt. Bd., 1942-1946 (Box 74, Folder 1a-1b)
  I.c.w. Hyman D. Langer.
- Joint Board. and D.C. Toronto Jt. Bd., 1940-1941 (Box 74, Folder 2)
- Joint Board. and D.C. Toronto Jt. Bd., 1937-1939 (Box 74, Folder 3a-3c)
  Incl. report on Canadian Cloak Markets by Thomas Cohen.
- Joint Board. and D.C. Toronto Jt. Bd., 1935-1936 (Box 74, Folder 4a-4c)
- Joint Board. and D.C. Toronto Jt. Bd., 1934 (Box 75, Folder 1a-1b)
  Incl. correspondence. on Toronto Labour Lyceum Assoc.
- Joint Board. and D.C. Toronto Jt. Bd., 1933 (Box 75, Folder 2)
- Joint Board. and D.C. Twin- Cities Jt. Bd., 1942-1950 (Box 75, Folder 3a)
  I.c.w. Michael Finkelstein, Dolores Johnson.
- Joint Board. and D.C. Twin Cities Jt. Bd., 1940-1941 (Box 75, Folder 3b)
  Incl. correspondence. on Cartwright Dress Co.
- Joint Board. and D.C. Twin Cities Jt. Bd., 1936-1939 (Box 75, Folder 4a-4b)
- Joint Board. and D.C. Twin Cities Jt. Bd., 1934-1935 (Box 75, Folder 5a-5b)
  I.c.w. Sander Genis; affidavits signed by workers against firms who did not adhere to dress code, 1934.
- Joint Board. and D.C. Winnipeg Jt. Bd., 1950 (Box 75, Folder 6)
  I.c.w. Sam Herbst.
- Justice, 1938-1939 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  Incl. 'Advertising Plan for Justice,' from Max Danish (Editor).
- Justice, 1937 (Box 76, Folder 2a-2b)
- Justice, 1936 (Box 76, Folder 3a-3b)
- K, 1940-1950 (Box 76, Folder 4a-4b)
- K, 1933-1939 (Box 76, Folder 5)
- Katovsky, Abraham, 1934-1945 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  Incl. correspondence. re his sickness & death.
- Kirtzman, Nicholas (Box 77, Folder 2)
- L, 1947-1951 (Box 77, Folder 3a-3b)
- L, 1940-1946 (Box 77, Folder 4a-4b)
- L, 1933-1939 (Box 77, Folder 5a-5c)
  I.c.w. Herbert Lehman on Union-related matters, 1933
- Labor Chest. Domestic, 1933-1937 (Box 77, Folder 6a-6b)
  Incl. correspondence., reports, financial statements & publications.
- Labor Department, U.S., 1934-1936 (Box 78, Folder 1)
- Labor Dept., U.S., 1933 (Box 78, Folder 2)
  I.c.w. Frances Perkins.
- Labor League for Human Rights, 1940-1946 (Box 78, Folder 3a-3d)
  Incl. minutes, resolutions on war relief, publications, agreements among organizations on aiding war victims, text of speech by Sir Walter Citrine, Dec. 1940 and correspondence.
- Labor Management Conference, Washington, 1945 (Box 78, Folder 4a-4b)
  Nov. 1945. (Called by Harry Truman) Incl. reports on labor conditions in numerous countries; list of delegates from AFL & CIO; proposed agenda.
- Labor Spy Activities, 1936-1940 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  Incl. memorandum on LaFollette Comm., by Research Dept. of Union, 1940. replies to Union questionnaire from officers on spying activities.
- Labor Stage, 1941-1944 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  Incl. broadcast of 'Labor for Victory' by Ben Hecht, 1942.
- Labor Stage, 1936-1945 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  I.c.w. Louis Shaffer (Manager); text of "Governor Altgeld" play by Melvin Levy.
- Labor Stage. ILGWU Dramatics. "Let Freedom Swing.", 1940 (Box 79, Folder 4)
  Incl. program & song sheet, 'Let Freedom Swing.'
- Labor Stage. Invitations to Ninth Annual Concert and Pageant, 1943 (Box 79, Folder 5)
- Labor Stage. "Labor Pains," Los Angeles, 1939-1940 (Box 79, Folder 6)
- Labor Stage. "Pins and Needles", 1937 (Box 79, Folder 7)
  Nov. 1937. Acceptances & declinations to N.Y. opening, arranged alphabetically by correspondence.
- Labor Stage. "Pins and Needles", 1938 (Box 79, Folder 8)
  Newspaper clipping files, N.Y.
- Labor Stage. "Pins and Needles", 1939 (Box 79, Folder 9a-9b)
  Invitations for a Second Showing.
- Labor Stage. "Pins and Needles", 1938 (Box 80, Folder 1)
  On tour, Boston to Los Angeles, arranged by city; incl. clippings.
- Labor Stage. "Pins and Needles", 1938-1939 (Box 80, Folder 2)
  On tour, Milwaukee to Providence.
- Labor Stage. "Pins and Needles", 1938-1939 (Box 80, Folder 3a-3b)
  1938-June 20, 1939, N.Y.C. Incl. correspondence. re radio talk by D.D. on educational and recreational activities of Union, April 15, 1938; correspondence. re broadcast of "Pins & Needles", Dec. 2, 1937.
- Labor Stage. "Pins and Needles", 1938-1941 (Box 80, Folder 4)
  On tour, Rochester to Wash., D.C., England and Canada.
- Labor Stage. Windsor Theatre, 1939-1940 (Box 80, Folder 5)
- LaGuardia, Fiorello, 1933-1950 (Box 80, Folder 6a-6b)
  Incl. LaGuardia plan for settling labor disputes, 1946, & correspondence.
- Harry Langer- Canadian Organizer, 1935-1937 (Box 80, Folder 7)
  Incl. report re dress situation in Montreal, 1936.
- Legislation, 1935-1945 (Box 81, Folder 1)
  Incl. correspondence. on Nat'l. Labor Relations Act & Board; Nat'l. Service Act, 1945.
- Legislation. Social Security, 1936-1937 (Box 81, Folder 2)
- Legislation. Supreme Court Reform, 1937 (Box 81, Folder 3a-3b)
  Corres. on Roosevelt's proposal to reform Supreme Court? letters written by Union officers to Congressmen & Senators.
- Legislation. Tariff and Trade Treaties, 1940 (Box 81, Folder 4)
  Incl. resolutions adopted by Union on Reciprocal Trade-Agreements Program.
- Legislation. Unemployment Insurance, 1937-1945 (Box 81, Folder 5)
- Legislation. Wages and Hours Bill, 1939-1943 (Box 81, Folder 6)
- Legislation. Wages and Hours Bill, 1937-1938 (Box 81, Folder 7a-7b)
  Corres. w. Merle Vincent & Elias Lieberman on passage of bill
- Legislation. Wages and Hours Bill, 1935-1936 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  Incl. statement by Wm. Green before Senate Judiciary Comm. on thirty-hour week, 1935.
- Legislation. Wages and Hours. Apparel Comm., 1939-1941 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  I.c.w. Burton E. Oppenheim (Director), Industry Comm. Branch of Wages & Hours Division.
- Legislation. Wages and Hours. Apparel Comm. (Box 82, Folder 3)
  Incl. reports on individuals for public membership on Apparel Industry Comm.
- Legislation. Wages and Hours. Outerwear Comm., 1939-1941 (Box 82, Folder 4)
  Corres. on outerwear industry.
- Legislation. Wages and Hours. Knitted Underwear Comm., 1939-1942 (Box 82, Folder 5)
  Incl. correspondence. & releases from Dept. of Labor.
- Legislation. Wages and Hours. Learner Exemptions Comm., 1939-1942 (Box 82, Folder 6a-6b)
  Corres. on modification of wages & hours for learners.
- Legislation. Wages and Hours. Other Industry Comm., 1939-1943 (Box 82, Folder 7)
- Legislation. Wages and Hours. Puerto Rico Industry Comm., 1941 (Box 82, Folder 8)
- Legislation. Wages and Hours. Puerto Rico Industry Comm., 1940 (Box 83, Folder 1a-1b)
- Legislation. Wages and Hours. Violations, 1938-1942 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  Industry & Union requests for investigations arranged alphabetically by cities, A-L.
- Legislation. Wages and Hours. Violations, M-Z. (Box 83, Folder 3)
- Lehman, Herbert H., 1936-1940 (Box 83, Folder 4)
- Lehman, Herbert H., 1930-1935 (Box 83, Folder 5)
  Incl. correspondence. on impending strike in cloak industry & memorandum by Cloak Jt. Bd. to Governor on strike, 1935.
- Lieberman, Elias, 1936-1939 (Box 83, Folder 6a-6b)
- Lieberman, Elias, 1933-1935 (Box 83, Folder 7a-7b)
- Local 6, Union City, N.J., 1933-1934 (Box 84, Folder 1)
  Embroidery Workers.
- Local 8, San Francisco, Calif., 1929-1933 (Box 84, Folder 2)
  1929-Jan. 1933. Cloak & Dressmakers. Incl. Charles M. Schwartzberg correspondence. on Communist activities, 1932; correspondence. w. Abraham Plotkin & J. Mencoff; some w. Benjamin Schlesinger.
- Local 9, N.Y., 1933-1942 (Box 84, Folder 3a-3b)
  Cloak & Suit Tailors Union. I.c.w. Isidore Sorkin, Burnet Cooper; GEB decision on charges brought by members of Locals 1, 9, 35 against Exec. Bd. of Local 9, 1934.
- Local 10, N.Y., 1933-1939 (Box 84, Folder 4a-4b)
  Amalgamated Ladies' Garment Cutters Union. I.c.w. Samuel Perlmutter.
- Local 10, 1939 (Box 84, Folder 5)
  Election.
- Local 17. (See Local 117) (Box 84, Folder 5a)
- Local 20, N.Y., 1933-1939 (Box 84, Folder 6)
  Waterproof Garment Workers Union. I.c.w. Joe Kessler.
- Local 22, N.Y., 1933-1939 (Box 84, Folder 7a-7b)
  Dressmakers Union. Corres. w. Charles S. Zimmerman.
- Local 23, N.Y., 1933-1939 (Box 85, Folder 1)
  Skirt Makers Union. Corres. w. Louis Reiss.
- Local 24, Boston, Mass, 1933-1938 (Box 85, Folder 2)
  Corres. w. Nathan H. Barker.
- Local 25, N.Y., 1933-1939 (Box 85, Folder 3)
  Blouse & Waistmakers Union. I.c.w. Charles Kreindler.
- Local 30, N.Y., 1933-1939 (Box 85, Folder 4)
  Designers Guild of Ladies Apparel. Corres. w. Joseph A. Valicenti.
- Local 31, N.Y., 1934-1942 (Box 85, Folder 5a-5b)
  Dress Patternmakers' Union (merged w. Local 10, Dec. 1942). I.c.w. M. Schwartzstein & Daniel Nisnavitz.
- Local 32, N.Y., 1934-1939 (Box 85, Folder 6)
  Corset & Brassiere Workers Union. I.c.w. Abraham Snyder.
- Local 35, N.Y., 1933-1939 (Box 85, Folder 7)
  Cloak, Skirt & Dress Pressers Union. Corres. w. Joseph Breslaw.
- Local 38, N.Y., 1933-1939 (Box 85, Folder 8)
  Ladies Tailors Custom Dressmakers, Theatrical Costume & Alteration Workers Union.
- Local 40, 1934-1939 (Box 86, Folder 1)
  Belt Makers Union. Corres. w. Henry Schwartz.
- Local 48, N.Y., 1933-1947 (Box 86, Folder 2a-2b)
  Italian Cloak, Suit, & Skirtmakers Union. Corres. w. Edward Molisani.
- Local 60, N.Y., 1933-1939 (Box 86, Folder 3)
  Dress & Waist Pressers' Union. I.c.w. Max Cohen.
- Local 60, 1935 (Box 86, Folder 4a-4b)
  Aug-Sept. 1935. Philip Kolinsky & Charles Cherkes case.
- Local 62, N.Y., 1933-1939 (Box 86, Folder 5)
  Undergarment & Negligee Workers Union. I.c.w. Samuel Shore.
- Local 63, Cleveland, O., 1933-1939 (Box 86, Folder 6a-6b)
  Coat, Suit & Dressmakers Union. I.c.w. Abraham W. Katovsky & David Solomon.
- Local 64, N.Y., 1933-1938 (Box 87, Folder 1)
  Cloak Buttonhole Makers Union.
- Local 66, N.Y., 1933-1939 (Box 87, Folder 2a-2b)
  Bonnaz, Embroideries, Tucking, Pleating, Allied Crafts Union. I.c.w. Leon Hattab.
- Local 67, Toledo, O., 1933-1939 (Box 87, Folder 3a-3b)
  Cloakmakers Union. I.c.w. Morris J. Cohen & Abraham Katovsky.
- Local 70, Portland, Ore., 1933-1939 (Box 87, Folder 4a-4b)
  Cloakmakers Union. I.c.w. Manly Labby.
- Local 72, Toronto, Canada, 1941-1946 (Box 87, Folder 5a-5b)
  Dressmakers Union. I.c.w. S. Kraisman, on internal local problems.
- Local 72, 1936-1940 (Box 88, Folder 1a-1b)
  Corres. & petitions re local elections, local conditions.
- Local 72, 1938-1940 (Box 88, Folder 2a-2b)
  Nov. 1938-July 1940. Special GEB Comm. to investigate Local situation.
- Local 74, Chicago, Ill., 1934-1937 (Box 88, Folder 3)
  Dress Pattern Makers. Chartered 3-27-34; out of existence, 8-25-42.
- Local 75, Worcester, Mass, 1933-1937 (Box 88, Folder 4)
  Cloak, Skirt, Dressmakers Union.
- Local 76, Chicago, Ill, 1938-1944 (Box 88, Folder 5a-5b)
  White Goods Workers Union. I.c.w. Morris Bialis & Abraham Plotkin on organizing activities in Smoler Bros. firm; Reconstruction Finance Corp. loan to Roberta Jill Co.
- Local 76, 1937 (Box 88, Folder 6)
- Local 76, 1933-1936 (Box 89, Folder 1a-1b)
  Corres. w. Abraham Plotkin & William W. Gaskin.
- Local 82, N.Y., 1933-1939 (Box 89, Folder 2)
  Examiners, Begraders & Bushlers Union.
- Local 88, Philadelphia, Pa., 1933-1939 (Box 89, Folder 3)
  I.c.w. Morris Fishman.
- Local 89, N.Y., 1933-1944 (Box 89, Folder 4a-4b)
  Italian Dress & Waistmakers Union. Corres. w. Luigi Antonini.
- Local 90, Elgin, Ill, 1932-1937 (Box 89, Folder 5)
- Local 91, N.Y., 1936-1946 (Box 89, Folder 6)
  Childrens Dress, Infants Wear, Housedress & Bathrobe Makers Union. Corres. re H.L. Hoffman Co. & Joseph L. Love, Inc.
- Local 91, 1939-1945 (Box 90, Folder 1a-1b)
  Corres. w. Harry Greenberg.
- Local 91, 1933-1938 (Box 90, Folder 2a-2b)
- Local 93, Reading, Pa., 1933-1939 (Box 90, Folder 3)
- Local 99, N.Y., 1934-1939 (Box 90, Folder 4a-4b)
  Ladies Apparel Shipping Clerks Union, affiliated w. United Hebrew Trades. Incl. correspondence. re affiliation w. Union.
- Local 102, N.Y., 1934-1941 (Box 90, Folder 5a-5b)
  Cloak, Dress, Drivers & Helpers Union. Corres. w. Saul Metz; N.Y. Dress Jt. Bd. complaint against Local 102; brief in behalf of Local 102, c. 1940.
- Local 91, Los Angeles, Calif, 1939 (Box 91, Folder 1)
  Designers Guild. Chartered, 3-15-35; out of existence, 1-30-39.
- Local 108, Harrisburg, Pa., 1933-1935 (Box 91, Folder 2)
- Local 115, Martinsburg, W. Va., 1934-1935 (Box 91, Folder 3)
- Local 116, Ft. Wayne, Ind., 1933-1938 (Box 91, Folder 4)
- Local 117, N.Y., 1936-1939 (Box 91, Folder 5)
  United Cloak, Suit, Infants & Childrens Coat Operators & Sample Makers Union. Corres., hearing re 1939 Local elections.
- Local 117, N.Y. Local 1, N.Y., 1933-1936 (Box 91, Folder 6)
  Cloak & Suit Operators Union (prior to merger).
- Local 120, 1935-1938 (Box 92, Folder 1)
- Local 120, 1933-1935 (Box 92, Folder 2)
- Local 121, 1939-1940 (Box 92, Folder 3)
- Local 122, 1939-1940 (Box 92, Folder 4)
- Local 122, 1937-1939 (Box 92, Folder 5)
- Local 122, 1937 (Box 92, Folder 6)
- Local 122, 1936 (Box 92, Folder 7)
- Local 122, 1936 (Box 92, Folder 8)
- Local 122, 1936 (Box 93, Folder 1)
  Jan-May 1936. Corres. w. Thomas E. Evans.
- Local 122, 1934-1935 (Box 93, Folder 2a-2b)
- Local 122, 1933 (Box 93, Folder 3)
- Local 122, 1935-1946 (Box 93, Folder 4a-4c)
  Corres. w. Joseph Jacobs (Atty., Director of Labor Service Bureau).
- Local 124, Kansas City, Mo., 1933-1936 (Box 94, Folder 1)
  Out of existence 2-4-37.
- Local 124, N.Y., 1933-1939 (Box 94, Folder 2)
  Plastic, Button & Novelty Workers Union.
- Local 142, N.Y., 1933-1939 (Box 94, Folder 3)
  Ladies Neckwear Workers Union.
- Local 155, N.Y., 1940-1941 (Box 94, Folder 4)
  Knitgoods Workers Union. Corres. w. Louis Nelson, financial reports.
- Local 155, 1937-1939 (Box 94, Folder 5a-5b)
  Incl. correspondence., printed material on 1939 Local election.
- Local 155, 1936 (Box 94, Folder 6)
- Local 155, 1924-1935 (Box 95, Folder 1a-1b)
  Corres. on jurisdictional dispute bet. Local and United Textile Workers of America, 1933-34; 1934 Knitgoods strike.
- Local 164, Bridgeport, Ct., 1936-1937 (Box 95, Folder 2)
- Local 175, Conneaut, O., 1934-1939 (Box 95, Folder 3)
  I.c.w. Abraham W. Katovsky.
- Local 178, Fall River, Mass., 1933-1938 (Box 95, Folder 4)
- Local 179, Boston, Mass. (Box 95, Folder 5)
  Chartered Mar. 1934? out of existence Feb. 1936? superseded by Local 229.
- Local 180 (and Local 123), 1934-1937 (Box 95, Folder 6)
- Local 190, Phila., Pa., 1934-1939 (Box 95, Folder 7)
  Knitgoods Workers Union.
- Local 191, San Francisco, Calif., 1939-1945 (Box 95, Folder 8a-8b)
  Knitgoods Workers Union. Case, Gantner & Mattern vs ILGWU; I.c.w. Jennie Matyas.
- Local 191, 1937-1939 (Box 95, Folder 9)
- Local 192, Lowell, Mass, 1935 (Box 96, Folder 1)
  Chartered Nov. 1934? out of existence, Mar. 1935.
- Local 193, Grand Rapids, Mich., 1937-1938 (Box 96, Folder 2)
  Knitgoods Workers Union. Chartered June 17, 1937; out of existence. June 7, 1939.
- Local 194, Portland, Ore., 1937 (Box 96, Folder 3)
  Knitgoods Workers Union. Chartered 7-15-37? out of existence, 12-8-38.
- Local 200, Cleveland, O., 1935-1937 (Box 96, Folder 4)
  Cloak & Suit Makers Union. Corres. w. Union officers re the Printz, Biederman Co.
- Local 207, Laredo, Tex., 1935-1937 (Box 96, Folder 5)
- Local 210, Kent, O., 1934 (Box 96, Folder 6)
- Local 214, Houston, Tex., 1935-1938 (Box 96, Folder 7)
- Local 216, Winnipeg, Can., 1940-1946 (Box 96, Folder 8a-8b)
  Cloakmakers Union. Corres. w. Samuel Herbst.
- Local 216, 1936-1939 (Box 96, Folder 9a-9b)
- Local 216, 1934-1935 (Box 96, Folder 10a-10b)
  Corres. w. S. Herbst on organizing Cloakmakers & relations w. Needle Trades Workers Industrial Union.
- Local 218, Jellico, Tenn., 1935-1936 (Box 97, Folder 1)
  Chartered 11-1-35; out of existence, 10-10-36.
- Local 233, Woonsocket, R.I. (Box 97, Folder 2)
  Chartered 4-18-36; out of existence, 9-12-39.
- Local 235, Salisbury, N.C., 1936 (Box 97, Folder 3)
  Corres. w. C.P. Barringer (Atty) on organizing the Sparrow Garment Co.
- Local 236, Los Angeles, Calif. (Box 97, Folder 4)
  Chartered 5-11-36; out of existence, 4-11-39.
- Local 238, Gary, Ind. Cotton Garment Workers Union. (Box 97, Folder 5)
  Chartered 3-16-37; out of existence, 10-3-38.
- Local 239, Meridian, Miss., 1936 (Box 97, Folder 6)
- Local 250, Kansas City, Mo., 1935-1938 (Box 97, Folder 7)
  Corres. on organizing Stern, Slegman & Prins Co.
- Local 262, Montreal, Can., 1937-1939 (Box 97, Folder 8a-8b)
  Dressmakers Union, Incl. correspondence. w. Bernard Shane on Rose Dress Mfg. Co. strike 1939.
- Local 266, Los Angeles, Calif., 1945-1947 (Box 97, Folder 9a-9b)
  Cotton Garment Workers Union. Chartered 1-15-37. Corres. w. Louis Levy.
- Local 266, 1943-1944 (Box 97, Folder 10)
- Local 266, 1940-1942 (Box 98, Folder 1)
- Local 267, Memphis, Tenn. (Box 98, Folder 2)
  Chartered 1-18-37? out of existence, 12-10-40.
- Local 271, Lexington, Mo. (Box 98, Folder 3)
  Chartered 3-10-37; out of existence, 8-5-38.
- Local 275, Zion City, Ill. (Box 98, Folder 4)
  Chartered 3-31-37? out of existence, 3-14-38.
- Local 276, Vancouver, B.C., Can, 1937-1939 (Box 98, Folder 5)
  Corres. w. Roland Jackson.
- Local 277, Indianapolis, Ind, 1937-1938 (Box 98, Folder 6)
- Local 278, Jackson, Miss. (Box 98, Folder 7)
  Chartered 4-12-37? out of existence, 10-7-38.
- Local 279, Lima, O., 1933-1938 (Box 98, Folder 8)
- Local 282, Boston, Mass. Knitgoods and Sportswear Workers Union. (Box 98, Folder 9)
  Chartered 7-1-37? out of existence, 1-20-39.
- Local 284, New Albany, Ind. (Box 98, Folder 10)
  Chartered 4-22-37; out of existence, 6-7-39.
- Local 286, Forrest City, Ark. (Box 98, Folder 11)
  Chartered 5-31-37; out of existence, 9-22-38.
- Local 293, Muskegon, Mich. (Box 98, Folder 12)
  Chartered 12-14-37; out of existence, Oct. 1941.
- Local 295, Cleveland, O., 1937 (Box 98, Folder 13a-13b)
  Corres. w. Union officers, Wm. Green on Knitgoods strike & jurisdictional controversy in knitgoods industry.
- Local 300, Puerto Rico, 1934-1940 (Box 111, Folder 1a-1c)
  May 1934-40. I.c.w. Teresa Angler, Needle Workers Union of Puerto Rico (ILGWU).
- Local 305, Port Huron, Mich., 1941-1948 (Box 111, Folder 2)
- Local 310, Berwick, Pa., 1938 (Box 111, Folder 3)
  Out of existence Jan. 20, 1939.
- Local 311, Toronto, Canada, 1937-1938 (Box 111, Folder 4)
  I.c.w. Hyman D. Langer. Out of existence April 11, 1939.
- Local 313, Brazil, Ind., 1937-1942 (Box 111, Folder 5)
  Out of existence Aug. 25, 1942.
- Local 314, Lacrosse, Wise., 1937-1938 (Box 111, Folder 6)
  Out of existence Nov. 18, 1940.
- Local 318, Detroit, Mich, 1935-1939 (Box 111, Folder 7)
  Incl. correspondence. re American Lady Corset Co.
- Local 322, Tupelo, Miss., 1937-1938 (Box 111, Folder 8)
  Out of existence, Feb. 8, 1939.
- Local 325, Huntington, W. Va., 1937-1939 (Box 111, Folder 9)
  Out of existence July ?, 1939.
- Local 326, Chambersburg, Pa., 1939-1940 (Box 111, Folder 10)
  Out of existence Mar. 4, 1940.
- Local 329 (also Local 122), Greensboro, N.C., 1937-1938 (Box 111, Folder 11)
  I.c.w. Dovie Atkins; out of existence Mar. 17, 1939.
- Local 335, Waynesboro, Pa., 1938 (Box 111, Folder 12)
  Out of existence April 21, 1939.
- Local 339, Miami, Fla., 1948-1949 (Box 112, Folder 1a-1d)
  I.c.w. Harry Rosenoff, Samuel Macy, Feigel L. Ronson.
- Local 339, Miami, Fla., 1942-1947 (Box 112, Folder 2a-2b)
  I.c.w. Herman Fried.
- Local 339, Miami, Fla., 1941 (Box 112, Folder 3)
  Corres. on organizing & chartering local.
- Local 341, San Francisco, Calif, 1938-1949 (Box 112, Folder 4)
  Chinese Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. I.c.w. Jennie Matyas, re organizing Chinese workers.
- Local 344, Chanute, Kansas, 1938 (Box 113, Folder 1)
  Corres.; out of existence, Feb. 15, 1939.
- Local 346, Chattanooga, Tenn, 1936-1939 (Box 113, Folder 2)
  Corres. on organizing.
- Local 348, St. Louis, Mo., 1938-1939 (Box 113, Folder 3)
- Local 351, Louisville, O., 1938-1939 (Box 113, Folder 4)
  Out of existence, Sept. 19, 1939.
- Local 352, San Francisco, Calif, 1938-1940 (Box 113, Folder 5)
- Local 354, Alpena, Mich., 1936-1940 (Box 113, Folder 6a-6b)
  I.c.w. Abraham Plotkin; out of existence, Sept. 2, 1941.
- Local 354, Alpena, Mich, 1939-1940 (Box 113, Folder 7a-7b)
  Strike; incl. newspaper clippings.
- Local 358, Crawfordsville, Ind., 1941 (Box 113, Folder 8)
  Jan-Feb. 1941. Out of existence, July 2, 1941.